{
    "response_code": 0,
    "results": [
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "You can legally drink alcohol while driving in Mississippi.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "In 2010, Twitter and the United States Library of Congress partnered together to archive every tweet by American citizens.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "All strawberries are red.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "&quot;Ananas&quot; is mostly used as the word for Pineapple in other languages.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "Video streaming website YouTube was purchased in it&#039;s entirety by Facebook for US$1.65 billion in stock.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "Did Michael Jackson invent the moonwalk?",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "Romanian belongs to the Romance language family, shared with French, Spanish, Portuguese and Italian. ",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "French is an official language in Canada.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "Ping-Pong originated in England",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "The color orange is named after the fruit.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        }
    ]
}